more of an East
Coast Hufflepuff.
I've made a critical error
on my Airbnb reservation.
This is not what the website
looked like at all.
I love the decor though.
I had no idea
hopeless was a color.
Hard left, douchebag.
Please, after you.
Another disgusting
minority off the streets.
We'll sleep well tonight.
Let's get a bagel.
Nighty-night, you
annoying prick!
You're a long way from
your superpowers.
Yeah. Just a touch of cancer.
Not to worry, we're old friends.
Fuck!
I wanted to be a superhero.
Always wanted a real super suit.
What happened?
When was the last time you
saw a plus-sized superhero?
Never.
The industry discriminates.
Fuck superheroes.
The thing that pisses
me off the most...
I never stood up for
myself in there.
My whole life.
I've been waiting for someone
to come and save me.
Nobody's gonna sacrifice
anything for me.
I gotta start taking
care of myself.
I have a mission now.
The first thing I wanna do
when I get out of here...
burn the headmaster alive...
and then take a selfie with
his smoldering corpse.
Aw. That's, like, my
favorite part of the Bible.
I don't have a sock
puppet on me...
but what did he do to you?
Did he taste the rainbow?
I'd whisper it, but
Skittles would sue us.
Fucker hates mutants.
He tried to beat the
genes out of us.
Nothing worse than a "pray
the gay away" type guy.
Sick piece of shit.
Tomorrow, we'll find the
biggest guy in here...
and we'll make him our bitch!
What was that?
That is the biggest guy in here.
Fun fact about the Ice Box...
though no one's ever seen it,
they keep a monster
in the basement.
Right next to a huge,
steaming bowl of foreshadowing.
Look.
I can't protect you.
With this collar on,
my superpower is just
unbridled cancer.
Give me a bow and arrow,
I'm basically Hawkeye.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
I've got tumors to grow.
Vanessa awaits.
I'll start by making us a shank.
Good listening. I stole
that guard's pen...
and stashed it in the
old prison wallet,
if you know what I'm saying.
I really hope I don't
know what you're saying.
I know it's in there, I
just need to get it out.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
I can hear you rummaging
around in there.
Do they make Purell
for your ears?
And to update you
on the story reported earlier,
after a lengthy standoff
outside the Essex House for
Mutant Rehabilitation...
two mutants were arrested
and transported
to the Ice Box...
Entering repair mode.
Several police cars
were destroyed
and the X-Men were called
in to restore order.
Cells seven and nine
now off-limits for
medical personnel.
Cells seven and nine
now off-limits for
medical personnel.
Psst!
Don't do that.
What? Why are you winking at me?
I got your back.
Oh, my God.
You're sick, I
gotta protect you.
Just leave me alone, kid.
Oh, great.
Well, hello there, new fish.
It's nice to see some
fresh faces around here.
I've done some light
catalog work...
but, really, modeling is just
a stepping stone to acting.
I was talking to him.Oh.
Have we met? I can't
place your mustache.
Black Tom Cassidy.
White Wade Wilson.
What's your superpower?
Cultural appropriation?
You're supposed to be the
toughest cunt in here.
You don't look like much to me.
First rule of the
yard, fuckface...
find the biggest guy
and make him your...
Second biggest guy.
The last thing I need
is more hepatitis.
Oh, it's slippery, too. This
table needs a wipe down!
Can we get a wipe
down on the table?
Kid, I think you
picked the wrong side.
No, I didn't! He's my friend!
Zip it. We're not friends.
You're about to
get dick-slapped.
I had so much fun!
You were like...
And I was like, "Take
a seat, shit dick."
Just let me die in peace.
We make a great team!
Oh, God! We're not a team.
Why'd you say that back there?
We're friends, partners.
We're not partners or friends.
This doesn't end with us
riding into the sunset.
It ends with me
dying of cancer...
and you winning the Ice Box
award for softest mouth.
There's only one
person in this world
that I care about,
and she's gone.
You wanna survive?
Stop trying to shank the
biggest guys in here...
and make friends with them.
Make friends with someone.
Anyone but me.
Maybe even Black Tim.
Black Evan, I don't know.
All I remember is he
was African-American.
System malfunctioning.
Cells 7, 12, 14, 27.
Back in your cells, you filthy mutants!
Get in there!
Cells 1, 3, 7, 8.
Searching.
Cell 04 located.
Door won't open!
On your fucking knees!
That was our cell.
What did I do to piss
off a grumpy old fucker
with a Winter Soldier arm?
Get away from me, kid!
Listen to me! Go!
Hello, Russell.
Who are you?
I'm Batman.
Ooh!
Oh. That's got some zip.
Don't feel bad. Even
I can't kill me.
Talk!
What kind of
spineless shit stick
tries to kill a 14-year-old boy?
You might wanna start talking!
'Cause I got a long history
of firing at times like this!
The name's Cable.
I'm from the future.
Just walk away.
Oh!
So, you're from the future.
I have three questions then.
One, is dubstep still a thing?
Two, do people still homebrew?
And three, does Dopinder
ever find love?
Dubstep's for pussies.
You're so dark!
Are you sure you're not
from the DC universe?
I love dubstep!
Is that a fanny pack?
I used to have one of
those in 1990-never.
Something to remember you by.
Give me that back! That
goes with me everywhere.
Like the memory of your
fucking fanny pack!
Why are you protecting the kid?
I don't give a fuck about him...
and his Are You My Mother?
Complex!
What's this one do?
In every film, there's a moment
when the hero hits rock bottom.
InCool Runnings, it
was when John Candy's
prized bobsled broke.
InHuman Centipede, it was
when those people...
signed on to be in that movie.
But in this film, well...
you're looking at it.
On your fucking knees, mutant.
Rock...
meet bottom.
I love you, Wade Wilson.
Ness?
Hey, Ness!
Ness, can you let me in?
Please! Please.
Jesus.
You're not giving me a
lot of direction here.
I'm at the end of my rope.
Then I joined the X-Men.
I went to prison. I, uh...
Is it the kid?
Kids give us a chance to be
better than we used to be.
The kid!
That's exactly what she meant.
Your heart needs to be
in the right place.
I'm not gonna abandon this kid.
He's never had anyone, ever.
I need to be selfless.
Yeah, but what does that mean?
It means I'm gonna save Russell.
Maybe I couldn't save Vanessa...
but maybe I can save a robust
teenager from New Zealand.
Yeah, but what I mean is,
like, the world "selfless."
I literally don't
know what that means.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, look. According
to my guy, okay...
those muties are
being transferred
to a supermax, 80 miles away.
Great, I'll pick 'em
off along the way.
Hold your testicles
there, buddy, okay?
We're talking about
an armored convoy...
and a vicious super soldier
from the future...
that is looking to turn your
skull into a fuckable ashtray.
You know what we need to do?
We need to build a fucking team.
We need 'em tough,
morally flexible...
and young enough
so they can carry
this franchise 10 to 12 years.
A team of highly-skilled
motherfuckers.
I'm talking about some Ocean's 14shit.
Rogue Two.
John Wick 3,but with
the original director.
My body is an
instrument of death.
Not now, Dopinder.
I could be of great use.
What's your superpower?
Courage. That's adorable.
Do you have the courage
to check and see...
if there are enough sanitary
napkins in the dispenser?
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry you had to see that,
although I'm glad you heard it.
All right, I'll put out
a call for resumes.
But we're not paying
medical or dental.
It's time to get
back on Linkedln.
Attention, all inmates!
Transport to Cross
Force Maximum Security
Mutant Containment Facility...
will begin at 0800 hours.
Inspection of your cells
and out processing
will begin at 0600.
Oi.
What the fuck do you want?
That's my fucking pudding.
Fuck your pudding!
You like pudding?
Hello?
I know you're in there.
Must be hard being the
biggest guy in here.